{
    "id": "ba3dc950b0814a84addeb0dd31915b2b",
    "title": "Common Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When I was talking to James, Susie ……………… our conversation.",
            "description": "To break in on a conversation is to interrupt it. ",
            "answers": [
                "broke out",
                "broke in on",
                "broke on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "James has agreed to ………………… the condition of my ancestral home every now and then.",
            "description": "To check up on something is to examine or investigate it. ",
            "answers": [
                "check on",
                "check up on",
                "check out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie has ………………… with an interesting suggestion.",
            "description": "To come up with something is to contribute. ",
            "answers": [
                "come out with",
                "come up with",
                "come with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you don’t want to fall into the debt trap, you should ..................... the money you spend on food and entertainment.",
            "description": "To cut down on expenses is to curtail them. ",
            "answers": [
                "cut down",
                "cut on",
                "cut down on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I hadn’t dropped ……………….. school at",
            "description": "To drop out of school is to leave school. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "out of",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He doesn’t get ………………… his siblings.",
            "description": "To get along with somebody is to have a good relationship with them. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "along",
                "along with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you think you can cheat on the exam and then get ………………… it?",
            "description": "To get away with something is to escape blame. ",
            "answers": [
                "on with",
                "away with",
                "out with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The politician tried hard to ……………….. his bad image.",
            "description": "To get rid of something is to eliminate it. ",
            "answers": [
                "get rid of",
                "get rid off",
                "get out of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me quite some time to get ………………. that assignment.",
            "description": "To get through with something is to finish it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "through",
                "through with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When they became rich, they started looking ……………… their neighbors.",
            "description": "To look down on somebody is to despise them. ",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "down on",
                "out on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. drunk drivers.",
            "description": "To look out for somebody or something is to anticipate them.",
            "answers": [
                "Look for",
                "Look out",
                "Look out for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not ……………….. any more nonsense.",
            "description": "To put up with something is to tolerate it. ",
            "answers": [
                "put with",
                "put up with",
                "put out with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}